teamweek.com 2017-05-23

# Privacy Policy - Teamweek

## Intro

Teamweek is committed to protect the privacy of our customers. This Privacy Policy outlines what information we collect and how we may use it on www.teamweek.com. If you have questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please feel free contact us at support@teamweek.com. 

###  Personal data 

When you sign up for an account in Teamweek we ask for your e-mail address and a password which will become your login credentials to sign in to Teamweek. We also ask for a company name, which will become a Teamweek domain name. 

We will do a best effort to deduce a user's display name from a user e-mail address. Users are able to change their display name any time through Planer interface. Display name is only used within your Teamweek account and on any printouts. Your display name is not provided to any user in other accounts or other third parties. 

Any other information collected within Teamweek is not mandatory and it will not be used outside your account or passed on to other third parties. 

We collect and store IP-address for each user for statistical purposes. Your IP-address will not be disclosed to any other third party. 

###  Cookies 

Teamweek uses a technology called "cookies" to store session information. This is a small file on your computer hard drive which will be created and accessed by your browser and contains an anonymous unique identifier. 

We currently use persistent cookies in Teamweek to store the login session ("Remember me"). A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. 

###  Payments 

Payments are handled by external service providers ("Adyen" and "Stripe"). You will be redirected to service provider website over secure link and you will enter all information necessary for payments there in secure manner. After payment you will be redirected to Teamweek automatically. 

Teamweek will not store your Credit Card number. Teamweek will store your billing address for receipt display purposes. 

###  Ad servers 

We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. We do not provide any user data to any ad server companies. 

###  Newsletters and other e-mail deliveries 

As part of the service Teamweek is sending out a periodic newsletter. Your name and e-mail address are used for sending the newsletter. You can opt out of receiving a newsletter by clicking a link within the newsletter itself. 

Teamweek will send a welcoming email to verify your new account. We also send out invitation e-mails to people you have invited to join your account. You can always request a password recovery email from Teamweek. 

We might email account administrators for billing related purposes. 

We will occasionally send out announcements related to Teamweek service in general. 

###  Blog 

If you use the Teamweek blog, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these blogs. Teamweek is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these blogs. 

###  Support forum 

If you post to the Teamweek Public Forums, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other forum visitors, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. Teamweek is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these blogs. 

Support requests sent by you through Teamweek feedback or support email will remain private. Some information (e.g. new features) in those requests can be published with your consent. 

###  Data Security 

Teamweek operates over Secure Sockets Layer protocol (HTTPS), so that the information exchange between you and Teamweek is encrypted. Teamweek only uses a valid SSL certificate from major service providers. 

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. 

###  Changes in Privacy Policy 

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.
